Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129
- Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.2 (1925: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.3 (1925: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.4 (1925: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.5 (1925: May)
  - Item 6: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.6 (1925: June)
  - Item 7: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.7 (1925: July)
  - Item 8: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.9 (1925: Sept.)
  - Item 9: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.10 (1925: Oct.)
  - Item 10: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.11 (1925: Nov.)
  - Item 11: Mixer and Server, 1925; Publication (Box 88, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.34:no.12 (1925: Dec.)
- Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.1 (1926: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.2 (1926: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.3 (1926: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.4 (1926: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.5 (1926: May)
  - Item 6: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.6 (1926: June)
  - Item 7: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.7 (1926: July)
  - Item 8: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.8 (1926: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.9 (1926: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.10 (1926: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.11 (1926: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Mixer and Server, 1926; Publication (Box 88, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no.12 (1926: Dec.)
- Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.1 (1929: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.2 (1929: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.3 (1929: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.4 (1929: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.5 (1929: May)
  - Item 6: Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.6 (1929: June)
  - Item 7: Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.7 (1929: july)
  - Item 8: Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.8 (1929: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Mixer and Server, 1929; Publication (Box 88, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.38:no.9 (1929: Sept.)
- The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Author: The National Underwriter Company
    Notes: v.28:no.39 (1924: Sept. 25)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.39A (1924: Sept. 25)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.40 (1924: Oct. 2)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.41 (1924: Oct. 9)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.41A (1924: Oct. 13)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.42 (1924: Oct. 16)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.43 (1924: Oct. 23)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.43A (1924: Oct. 24)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.44 (1924: Oct. 30)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.28:no.44A (1924: Oct. 30)
- The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.45 (1924: Nov. 6)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.46 (1924: Nov. 13)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.47 (1924: Nov. 20)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.48 (1924: Nov. 27)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.49 (1924: Dec. 4)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.50 (1924: Dec. 11)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.51 (1924: Dec. 18)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1924; Publication (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.28:no.52 (1924: Dec. 25)
- The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.1 (1925: Jan. 1)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.2 (1925: Jan. 8)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.3 (1925: Jan. 15)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.4 (1925: Jan. 22)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.4A (1925: Jan. 22)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.5 (1925: Jan. 29)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.6 (1925: Feb. 5)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.7 (1925: Feb. 12)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.8 (1925: Feb. 19)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.9 (1925: Feb. 26)
- The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.10 (1925: Mar. 5)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.10A (1925: Mar. 6)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.11 (1925: Mar. 12)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.12 (1925: Mar. 19)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.12, Part 2 (1925: Mar. 19)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.13 (1925: Mar. 26)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.13, Part 2 (1925: Mar. 26)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.14 (1925: Apr. 2)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.15 (1925: Apr. 9)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.16 (1925: Apr. 16)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.16, Part 2 (1925: Apr. 16)
  - Item 12: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.17 (1925: Apr. 23)
  - Item 13: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.18 (1925: Apr. 30)
- The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.29:no.19 (1925: May 7)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.29:no.20 (1925: May 14)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.29:no.21 (1925: May 21)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.29:no.22 (1925: May 28)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.29:no.23 (1925: June 4)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.29:no.24 (1925: June 11)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.29:no.25 (1925: June 18)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.29:no.26 (1925: June 25)
- The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.26A (1925: June 29)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.27 (1925: July 2)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.28 (1925: July 9)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.29 (1925: July 16)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.30 (1925: July 23)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.31 (1925: July 30)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.32 (1925: Aug. 6)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.33 (1925: Aug. 13)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.34 (1925: Aug. 20)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29:no.35 (1925: Aug. 27)
- The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.36 (1925: Sept. 3)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.36A (1925: Sept. 4)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.37 (1925: Sept. 10)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.38 (1925: Sept. 17)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.38A (1925: Sept. 18)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.39 (1925: Sept. 24)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.40 (1925: Oct. 1)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.41 (1925: Oct. 8)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.41A (1925: Oct. 9)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.42 (1925: Oct. 15)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.43 (1925: Oct. 22)
  - Item 12: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.43A (1925: Oct. 23)
  - Item 13: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.29:no.44 (1925: Oct. 29)
- The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.45 (1925: Nov. 5)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.46 (1925: Nov. 12)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.46A (1925: Nov. 13)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.47 (1925: Nov. 19)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.48 (1925: Nov. 26)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.49 (1925: Dec. 3)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.50 (1925: Dec. 10)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.51 (1925: Dec. 17)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.52 (1925: Dec. 24)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1925; Publication (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.53 (1925: Dec. 31)
- The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.1 (1926: Jan. 7)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.2 (1926: Jan. 14)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.3 (1926: Jan. 21)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.4A (1926: Jan. 27)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.4 (1926: Jan. 28)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.5 (1926: Feb. 4)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.6 (1926: Feb. 11)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.7 (1926: Feb. 18)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.8 (1926: Feb. 25)
- The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.9 (1926: Mar. 4)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.9A (1926: Mar. 5)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.10 (1926: Mar. 11)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.11 (1926: Mar. 18)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.12 (1926: Mar. 25)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.13 (1926: Apr. 1)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.13, Part 2 (1926: Apr. 1)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.13, Part 2 (1926: Apr. 1). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.14 (1926: Apr. 8)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.15 (1926: Apr. 15)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.15, Part 2 (1926: Apr. 15)
  - Item 12: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.16 (1926: Apr. 22)
  - Item 13: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 90, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.17 (1926: Apr. 29)
- The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.18 (1926: May 6)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.19 (1926: May 13)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.20 (1926: May 20)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.21 (1926: May 27)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.22 (1926: June 3)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.23 (1926: June 10)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.23A (1926: June 11)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.24 (1926: June 17)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.30:no.25 (1926: June 24)
- The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.26 (1926: July 1)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.27 (1926: July 8)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.28 (1926: July 15)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.29 (1926: July 22)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.30 (1926: July 29)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.31 (1926: Aug. 5)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.32 (1926: Aug. 12)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.33 (1926: Aug. 19)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.30:no.34 (1926: Aug. 26)
- The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.35 (1926: Sept. 2)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.36 (1926: Sept. 9)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.36A (1926: Sept. 10)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.36A, Extra Edition (1926: Sept. 13)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.37 (1926: Sept. 16)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.38 (1926: Sept. 23)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.38A (1926: Sept. 24)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.39 (1926: Sept. 30)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.40 (1926: Oct. 7)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.41 (1926: Oct. 14)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.42 (1926: Oct. 21)
  - Item 12: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.43 (1926: Oct. 28)
- The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.43A (1926: Nov. 1)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.44 (1926: Nov. 4)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.45 (1926: Nov. 11)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.46 (1926: Nov. 18)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.47 (1926: Nov. 25)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.48 (1926: Dec. 2)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.49 (1926: Dec. 9)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.50 (1926: Dec. 16)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.51 (1926: Dec. 23)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1926; Publication (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.30:no.52 (1926: Dec. 30)
- The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.1 (1927: Jan. 6)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.2 (1927: Jan. 13)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.3 (1927: Jan. 20)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.4 (1927: Jan. 27)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.4A (1927: Jan. 27)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.4 (1927: Feb. 3)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.5 (1927: Feb. 4)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.6 (1927: Feb. 10)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.7 (1927: Feb. 17)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.7 (1927: Feb. 18)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 91, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.8 (1927: Feb. 24)
- The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.10 (1927: Mar. 10)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.11 (1927: Mar. 17)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.11A (1927: Mar. 18)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.12 (1927: Mar. 24)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.13 (1927: Mar. 31)
  - Item 6: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.14 (1927: Apr. 7)
  - Item 7: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.14A (1927: Apr. 13)
  - Item 8: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.15 (1927: Apr. 14)
  - Item 9: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.15A (1927: Apr. 15)
  - Item 10: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.16 (1927: Apr. 21)
  - Item 11: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.17 (1927: Apr. 28)
- The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.31:no.18 (1927: May 5)
  - Item 2: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.31:no.19 (1927: May 12)
  - Item 3: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.31:no.20 (1927: May 19)
  - Item 4: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.31:no.21 (1927: May 26)
  - Item 5: The National Underwriter, 1927; Publication (Box 92, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.31:no.22 (1927: June 2)